Guide to the G. Ridgley Loux papers, 1974-1993
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
G. Ridgley Loux papers
1974-1993
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
G. Ridgley Loux
C0165
11.75 linear feet (24 boxes)
The G. Ridgley Loux papers contain records relating to commercial and residential development in Reston. The papers are from the Reston Community Association (RCA) Planning and Zoning Committee, Fairfax County Annual Plan Review Task Force, Reston Town Center Task Force, Fairfax Center Area Task Force, and other files on various issues relating to Reston projects.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated by G. Ridgley Loux in August, 1993.
Biographical Information
Robert E. Simon, Jr. purchased the land that later became Reston with the proceeds from the sale of Carnegie Hall in New York City in 1961. Construction began in 1963 with the building of Lake Anne. Simon wanted Reston to be a place where individuals could remain their entire lives, thus many different types of housing were constructed. In 1968 the Reston Community Association (RCA) was created to take responsibility for community programs. Between 1974 and 1993 G. Ridgley Loux collected documents from the Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning Committee and other projects in Reston development. During that time the Reston Community Association was incorporated with the Reston Homeowners Association under the name Reston Association.
Scope and Content
The G. Ridgley Loux papers contain records relating to commercial and residential development in Reston. The papers are from the Reston Community Association (RCA) Planning and Zoning Committee, Fairfax County Annual Plan Review Task Force, Reston Town Center Task Force, Fairfax Center Area Task Force, and other files on various issues relating to Reston projects.
Series one is titled committees. The majority of the papers in this series are divided monthly from 1980 to 1992 from the Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning Committee. The rest of the paperwork is from various other committees in Reston. The papers are information on various projects that the committees worked on. The series is dated from 1980 to 1993 and is contained in boxes 1 through 9.
Series two is titled reports. The papers in this series are reports on different projects in the Reston area. Those projects include transportation, budget, American Mobil Satellite Corporation (AMSC) and others. The series is dated from 1980 to 1993 and is contained in boxes 9 through 12.
Series three is titled plans. The papers in this series are plans from various developments and buildings projects in the Reston area. Some of the papers include plans for the Annual Plan Review, Hunter Mill, Town Center and other projects. The series is dated from 1981 to 1993 and is contained in boxes 12 through 19.
Series four is titled general information and is the final series in this collection. The papers cover a variety of topics dealing with building projects in Reston, such as Lake Anne, Dulles, Town Center and others. Also among the paperwork are brochures and information on the developments. The series dates from 1974 to 1993 and is contained in boxes 19 through 24.
Arrangement
Organized into four series.
Series 1: Committees, 1980-1993 (Boxes 1-9)
Series 2: Reports, 1980-1993 (Boxes 9-12)
Series 3: Plans, 1981-1993 (Boxes 12-19)
Series 4: General Information, 1974-1993 (Boxes 19-24)
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
The Special Collections and Archives also holds the Planned Community Archives and other personal papers and organizational records that document Reston, Virginia, and other planned communities.
Index Terms
Persons:
Loux, G. Ridgley.
Corporate Names:
Reston Association.
Geographical Names:
Reston (Va.)
Subjects:
Housing--Virginia--Reston.; Planned communities--Virginia--Reston.
Contents List
- Series 1: Committees, 1980-1993; (8.5 boxes)
  The majority of the papers in this series are from the Reston Community Association (RCA) Planning and Zoning Committee. The rest of the papers are information on various projects that the other committees worked on.
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, March 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    342.1
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, April 1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    342.2
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, May 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    342.3
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, June 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    342.4
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, July 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    342.5
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, August 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    342.6
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, September 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    342.7
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, October 1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    342.8
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, November 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    342.9
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, December 1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    342.10
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, January 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    342.11
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, February 1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    342.12
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, March 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    342.13
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, April 1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    342.14
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, May 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    342.15
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, June 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    342.16
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, July 1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    342.17
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, August 1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    342.18
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, September 1981 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    342.19
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, October 1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    342.20
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, November 1981 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    342.21
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning, December 1981 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    342.22
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, January 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    342.23
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, February 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    342.24
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, March 1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    342.25
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, April 1982 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    342.26
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, May 1982 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    342.27
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, June 1982 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    342.28
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, July 1982 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    342.29
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, August 1982 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    342.30
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, September 1982 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    342.31
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, October 1982 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    342.32
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, November 1982 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    342.33
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, December 1982 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    342.34
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, January 1983 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    342.35
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, February 1983 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    342.36
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, March 1983 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    342.37
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, April 1983 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    342.38
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, May 1983 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    342.39
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, June 1983 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    342.40
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, July 1983 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    342.41
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, August 1983 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    342.42
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, September 1983 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    342.43
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, October 1983 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    342.44
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, November 1983 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    342.45
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, December 1983 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    342.46
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, January 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    343.1
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, February 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    343.2
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, March 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    343.3
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, April 1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    343.4
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, May 1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    343.5
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, June 1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    343.6
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, July 1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    343.7
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, August 1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    343.8
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, September 1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    343.9
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, October 1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    343.10
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, November 1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    343.11
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, December 1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    343.12
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, January 1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    343.13
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, February 1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    343.14
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, March 1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    343.15
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, April 1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    343.16
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, May 1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    347.17
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, June 1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    343.18
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, July 1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    343.19
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, August 13 1985 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    343.20
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, September 1985 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    343.21
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, October 1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    343.22
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, November 1985 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    343.23
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, December 1985 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    343.24
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, January 14, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    344.1
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, February 11, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    344.2
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, March 11 and 31, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    344.3
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, April 8 and 22, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    344.4
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, May 13 and 27, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    344.5
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, June 10, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    344.6
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, July 8, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    344.7
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, August 12, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    344.8
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, September 9 and 23, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    344.9
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, October 14 and 28, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    344.10
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, November 11 and 25, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    344.11
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, December 9, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    344.12
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, January 13 and 27, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    344.13
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, February 10 and 24, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    344.14
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, March 10 and 12, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    344.15
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, April 14 and 28, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    344.16
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, May 12 and 26, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    344.17
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, June 9, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    344.18
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, July 14, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    344.19
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, August 11, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    344.20
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, September 8, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    344.21
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, October 13 and 22, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    344.22
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, November 10, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    344.23
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, December 8, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    344.24
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, January 12 and 26, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    345.1
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, February 10 and 23, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    345.2
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, March 8, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    345.3
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, April 12, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    345.4
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, May 10, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    345.5
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, June 13, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    345.6
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, July 12, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    345.7
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, August, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    345.8
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, September 13, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    345.9
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, October 1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    345.10
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, November 8, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    345.11
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, December 13, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    345.12
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, January 10 1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    345.13
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, February 14 1989 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    345.14
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, March 14 1989 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    345.15
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, April 11 1989 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    345.16
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, May 9 1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    345.17
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, June 13 1989 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    345.18
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, July 11 1989 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    345.19
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, August 8 1989 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    345.20
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, September 12 1989 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    345.21
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, October 10 1989 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    345.22
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, November 14 1989 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    345.23
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, December 1989 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    345.24
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, January 9 1990 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    345.25
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, February 13 1990 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    345.26
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, March 13 1990 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    345.27
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, April 10 1990 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    345.28
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, May 8 1990 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    345.29
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, June 12 1990 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    345.30
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, July 10 1990 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    345.31
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, August 1990 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    345.32
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, September 13 1990 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    345.33
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, October 9 1990 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    345.34
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, November 13 1990 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    345.35
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, December 1990 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    345.36
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, January 1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    346.1
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, February 1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    346.2
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, April 1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    346.3
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, May 1991 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    346.4
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, June 1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    346.5
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, July 1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    346.6
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, August 1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    346.7
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, September 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    346.8
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, October 1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    346.9
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, November 1991 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    346.10
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, December 1991 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    346.11
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    346.12
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    346.13
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    346.14
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, January 1992 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    346.15
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, February 1992 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    346.17
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, March 1992 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, April 1992 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    346.18
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, May 1992 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    346.19
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, June 1992 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    346.20
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, July 1992 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    346.21
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, August 1992 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    346.22
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, September 1992 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    346.23
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, October 1992 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    346.24
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, December 1992 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    346.25
  - Bond Relief Committee, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    347.9
  - Environmental Quality Advisory Council, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    411.4
  - Street Light Committee, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    356.1
  - Street Light Committee, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    355.13
  - Summary of Adopted Amendments, Fairfax County Planning Committee, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    351.1
  - Rezoning and Development, Reston, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    355.6
  - Environmental Quality Advisory Council: Toxic Chemicals Plan Amendment, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    354.10
  - Planning and Zoning, February through April 1986 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    352.2
  - Planning and Zoning: January through February, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    352.1
  - Environmental Quality Advisory Council I, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    356.3
  - Street Light Committee, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    355.12
  - Reston Inn and Conference Center Venture vs. The Board of Supervisors of Fairfax County, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    362.5
  - Fairfax County Goals and Advisory Commission, Final Report-December, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    354.1
  - Reston Forum, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    411.14
  - Planning Commission REcommendations, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    358.6
  - Citizens Committee, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    356.10
  - C and I District Zoning, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    362.3
  - Reston Land Corporation (RLC) Rezoning and Sunset HIlls Relocation, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    361.3
  - Parcel 12B-Turner Harwood, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    360.4
  - Reston Community Association (RCA) Planning and Zoning-General, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    359.7
  - C and I District Zoning, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    362.4
  - Reston Community Association (RCA) Board of Directors-Minutes, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    412.10
  - Reston Transportation Committee, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    412.11
  - Reston, Planning and Zoning, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    363.12
  - Reston, Planning and Zoning Committee, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    363.6
  - Martha Pennino, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    363.7
  - Reston, Planning and Zoning Committee, Golf Park Issue, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    364.1
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, January 1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    347.1
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, February 1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    347.2
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, March 1993 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    347.3
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, April 1993 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    347.4
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Committee, May 1993 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    347.5
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Park, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    363.5
  - Reston, Planning and Zoning, 1988 and 1990 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    363.1
  - Reston Planning and Zoning Miscellaneous Papers, 1985-1991 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    363.4
  - Planning and Development, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    351.10
  - Planning and Zoning (P and Z), 1982-1986 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    352.8
  - Planning and Zoning (P and Z), 1982-1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    352.7
  - Building and Development, Reston Area (newsclippings), 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    353.4
  - Planning and Zoning Committee, Fairfax County, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    350.7
  - Planning and Zoning Commission, Fairfax County, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    350.6
  - Planning and Zoning Commission, Fairfax County, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    350.5
  - Planning and Zoning Commission, Fairfax County, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    350.4
- Series 2: Reports, 1980-1993; (3 boxes)
  The papers in this series are reports on different projects in the Reston area. Those projects include transportation, American Mobil Satellite Corporation (AMSC) and others.
  - Building and Development-Reston, 1980-1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    347.14
  - Vepco, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    348.3
  - Traffic-Other Hunter Mill Road, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    357.6
  - Multifamily Residential Development: Study of Need and Availability in Fairfax County, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    355.3
  - Office and Industrial Development in Fairfax County-April, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    355.4
  - Shopping Centers-Meeting the Demand for Retail Commercial Facilities in Western Fairfax County, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    355.7
  - Staff Report-Proposed Zoning Ordinance Amendment, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    355.9
  - Miscellaneous Staff Reports, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    355.8
  - BAM/CIA Tower, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    354.8
  - Parking Reston, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    357.2
  - Business and Marketing, Reston, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    356.9
  - Transportation-Reston-Urban Land Institute (ULT)Seminars, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    359.3
  - Transportation-Reston, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    359.4
  - Goals Commission Report Recommendation for a Mayor Review of the Plan, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    358.5
  - Traffic-Other Hunter Mill Road, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    357.7
  - Centennial Site Citizens Task Force, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    412.4
  - EMTA FAcility on Route 7, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    361.1
  - Town Center, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    361.4a
  - Town Center, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    361.4b
  - Evans Sea, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    361.7
  - Evans Sea, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    362.1
  - Evans Sea, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    362.2a
  - Evans Sea, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    362.2b
  - Reston Land Corporation, Rezoning, May 1990 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    362.7
  - Planning and Rezoning Commission (PRC) Task Force, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    363.10
  - Planning and Rezoning Commission (PRC) Task Force, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    363.9
  - Planning and Rezoning Commission (PRC) Task Force, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    363.8
  - Fairfax County Budget Proposal, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    413.1
  - American Mobil Satellite Corporation (AMSC), 1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    413.3a
  - American Mobil Satellite Corporation (AMSC), 1992 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    413.3b
  - American Mobil Satellite Corporation (AMSC), 1993 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    413.2
- Series 3: Plans, 1981-1993; (7 boxes)
  The papers in this series are plans from various developments and buildings projects in the Reston area. Some of the papers include plans for Hunter Mill, Town Center and other projects.